# **Kenneth Rose**

## Software Developer / IT Technician

A driven and solution-oriented Computer Scientist and Mathematician with a rapidly expanding repertoire of professional skills. Developed a proficiency in numerous programming languages including Java, JavaScript, Python and C. Additionally, the experience as an IT Technician has developed strong communication, teamwork, and customer service skills. I am excited and prepared to enter the industry and get hands-on experience in programming, information security, and networking.

#### Contact

## Phone

(516) 359-1840

#### E-mail

rosekenny12@gmail.com

### Website | LinkedIn

## **Skills**

React	••••
Java	••••
Python	••••
С	•••00
SQL	•••00
Git	••••
Attention to detail	••••
Collaboration	•••••
Leadership	•••••
Problem solving	••••

## **Work History**

#### 2019-09 - Lead IT Technician

#### 2021-08

Stony Brook University, Stony Brook, NY

- Assist staff and students via telephone, email, helpdesk tickets, in-person visits, and remote access.
- Install, upgrade, troubleshoot and repair desktop computers, laptops, phones, IoT devices, etc.
- Managed team performance by training, motivating, and directing 20 employees.

## **Projects**

## **State Districting Application**

Full Stack

- Generate random sets of districting plans for the state on a high-performance computer, compare and analyze districting results based on objective function, and display concise and detailed results to the user.
- Generates fair districts based on census data, election result data, and geospatial data.

## **Education**

2017-08 - Bachelor of Science: Computer Science, Applied 2021-05 Mathematics

Stony Brook University - Stony Brook, NY

 Coursework in Object Oriented Programming, Data Structures, Analysis of Algorithms, Software Development, Computer Networks, and Database Systems

## **Accomplishments**

• Eagle Scout - Boy Scouts of America